## **KEVIN ADRIAN PILLAY**

#### IT System Administrator

- +31642060096 kevinadrianpl@gmail.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/kevinadrianpl/ https://kevinadrian.dev/
  - Rotterdam, The Netherlands References and qualifications are available on request.

### **Summary**

Experienced IT systems administrator and cybersecurity enthusiast with a history of working in multiple industries in roles such as IT management, server management, system administration, and information security. I am a South African currently residing in The Netherlands under a valid residence permit, and as a native English speaker, I'm actively learning Dutch while being legally eligible to work.

# **Work Experience**

All Steel Productions IT Manager	Richards Bay, KwaZulu-Natal, South Africa · Remote 10/2022 - Present
Novus Holdings Ltd (previously Paarl Media Group) IT System Administrator	Mandeni, KwaZulu-Natal, South Africa · On-site 09/2015 - 05/2022
Mactron Technology Network Technician	Eshowe, KwaZulu-Natal, South Africa · On-site 01/2013 - 12/2014
Genmac Engineering and Construction CC IT Technician	Richards Bay, KwaZulu-Natal, South Africa · On-site 10/2011 - 12/2012
S and N Projects Junior Technician	Richards Bay, KwaZulu-Natal, South Africa · On-site 02/2010 - 07/2011
Boston City Campus & Business College	Richards Bay, KwaZulu-Natal, South Africa · On-site

Education	
IT Academy - Optimi College Cybersecurity Specialist	01/2021 - 12/2022
University of South Africa/Universiteit van Suid-Afrika Information Technology	01/2010 - 12/2011
Boston City Campus Information Technology	01/2009 - 12/2010
Isandlwana Technical High School High School Diploma	01/2003 - 12/2008

## **Skills Summary**

System Administration: VMware (Hyper-V, Sphere) · Active Directory · PowerShell · Microsoft Server · Linux Administration · Backups (Veeam, Acronis)

Security: Incident Response · SIEM · Network Security · Risk Assessment · Firewalls · Security Policies · Endpoint Security · Metasploit

Technical Support: Documentation · Customer Service · OS Familiarity (Windows, Linux) · Networking (TCP/IP, DNS, DHCP) · Multitasking

Other: SQL/MySQL · Remote Desktop Services (RDS) · Scripting Languages (Python, Bash) · Microsoft Office · ERP Software · IT Management

01/2009 - 01/2010

Trainee